## **Abdullah Kilinc**

# Product Designer

I am Abdullah Kilinc, a product designer who loves to create new designs. I currently live in Turkey / Konya. Have been designing for 12 years and follow trends closely. I love to create new, simple and user friendly interface designs. I have 10 years of freelance and remote working experience.

The design categories I have designed successfully are as follows; User Interface Design, Mobile Application Interface Design, Logo Design

## **Experience**

## Godtebyen.no / Product Designer

MAY 2020 - PRESENT, REMOTE

A new responsive e-commerce interface was designed for the customer. Currently, i lead a team to maintain the internal style guide & impement new design patterns in. Docs, Sheeds & Slides on web & mobile. I create design prototypes for motion stuides, oversee production specs & facilitate design reviews with stakeholders across al the 3 apps. I calloborate closely with product managers, developers, resarchers & the marketing team.

## • Fiberkablonet.com / Product Designer

OCT. 2020 - PRESENT, REMOTE

We worked together on the customer's need for a new interface design. Adwords and social media spending are quite high on existing sites, but sales are low. With the new interface design work, we achieved an increase of 460% with the same ad spend. Turkey reached the highest sales figures in the category of 2020.

## Gencvizyon.com.tr / Product Designer

NOV. 2019 - APRIL 2020 REMOTE

User interface design studies were carried out for the special online education course.

freegrafiker.com info@freegrafiker.com +90 506 146 41 31

#### Skills

#### Design

- UI & UX design graphics
- Strategy & vision presentations
- User flows
- Concept sketches
- · Wireframes & mock ups with Sketch
- Campaing + Branding
- Project Management
- Wordpress

#### Collaboration

- Flexible
- Hard Worker
- Organizing workshops
- · Facilitating design critique
- Self starter
- Detail oriented
- Communicative

#### Education

Anadolu Uni. Eskişehir / TURKEY

AUG 2009 - MAY 2014

## Look Up/ Product Designer

MAY 2019 - NOV 2019 REMOTE

Preparation of user flows and all interface designs of the customer's mobile application project. Crafted UX flows, designed interfaces and conducted user studies.

Designed interfaces for location - based video sharing app on ios and android platform and worked with engineering team to finish implementation.

(still in the development process)

## Harvest Natural Market / UI - UX Design

MAY 2016 - The Mediatix / FULL TIME

Interface design I have prepared for the organic shopping center serving in Texas / Houston

https://freegrafiker.com/harvest-natural-market-web-arayuz-tasarim.html

#### Design Experience

I can use Mac and Windows systems at a professional level. I can design on a Mac and Windows operating system. I can do design work on Sketch, Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop apps.

I've worked with shared libraries in Sketch before. There are projects I have completed by the design systems rules.

I follow Adobe products and Figma updates closely.

### Wordpress Experience

My website, which I have been using, has been working with wordpress infrastructure for 8 years.

I have prepared and used 3 different wordpress themes for myself so far. I use paid and free plugins.

I designed an e-commerce interface design for Wordpress.

What am I doing on Wordpress? I create and publish content for my portfolio site. I regularly make backups and updates.

I only included a few projects here, please visit for more.

https://freegrafiker.com/